Preliminary guide to the James Goode papers, Circa 1860-2018 MS0670.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Washington Sculpture, circa 1970 - circa 2015; 2002-2008; Series 2; 15 Linear Feet
  - 15.17 Montross Crossing, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 15.18 Spirit of Rockville, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 15.19 Confederate Soldier, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - 15.20 American Pride, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 15.21 Hand of Noaa, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 15.22 The Communter, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 15.23 Pod of Tress, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 15.26 Mattie Stepanek, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - 15.27 Jim Henson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 15.29 James Rouse, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 15.30 Prince Georges Tricen Hourses, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 15.31 Mother and Child, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 15.32 Constitution Frieze, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 15.33 Vox Populi, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 15.34 Twin Arcs, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 15.35 Hyattsville Horn Section, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 15.36 Three Guardians, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ch. 15 - Great Awakening, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ch. 15 - The Awakening, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 15 - Dovetail, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Ch. 15 - Against the Day, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Ch. 15 - Moroni, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 15 - Maryland suburbs - not used - Cole Field House, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 16 Virginia suburbs, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 16.1 Dark Star Park, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 16.2 Cupids Garden, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 16.3 Anna and David, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 16.6 Bud/Blossom, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 16.7 Ben Franklin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 16.8 Thedore Roosevelt, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 16.9 Marine Corps War Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 16.10 Air Force Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 16.12 Richard Byrd, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 16.13 Seabees, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 16.14 101st Army Airborne Division, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 16.15 4th Infantry (IVY) Division, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 16.17 Tomb of the Unknowns, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 16.17 Women in Military Service Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 16.17 Arlington Cemetery, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 16.18 Confederate Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 16.19 Military Nurses, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 16.20 Phil Kearney, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 16.21 John Dill, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 16.26 Navy-Marine Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 16.30 Alexandria, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 16.33 Shipbuilder, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 16.34 American Elk, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 16.35 Appomattox, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 16.36 Brio, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 16.37 Generations, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 16.38 Promenade Classique, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 16.39 Rocky Versace, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 16.40 Justice Delayed, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - 16.41 D.D. Eisenhower, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - 16.42 W. Wilson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - 16.43 George Washington at Mt. Vernon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - 16.44 Kryptos, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - 16.45 Man Slopping Pigs, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - 16.46 George Mason at G.M. Univ., circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - 16.47 Communitas, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 16.48 Fountain of Faith, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 16.51 Camden Horse, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 16.52 Robert Simon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 16.53 Stonewall Jackson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 16.54 Ascent, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 16.55 Ascension, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 16.56 Herb and Muggs, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ch. 16 - Marine Corps Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Ch. 16 - Netherlands Carillon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Ch. 16 - Folded Circle Ring, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 16 - Shipbuilder, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 17.7 Boy Riding Goat, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 17.19 Ben Franklin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Outdoor sculpture - copy for James to check - 64 sculptors for research, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14A)
  - Abend, Harry - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Amateis, Edmond Rumulus - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bass, Thomas Dwyer - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Berks, Robert - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Block, Adolph - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Brackenridge, Marian - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Bush, Carol L. - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Calder, Alexander - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Cavanaugh, John - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Davis, Emma Lu - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - DeLue, Donald Harcourt - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - De Rivera, Jose - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - De Rosen, John Henry - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - De Weldon, Felix W. - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Donnelly, John James - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Hart, Frederick - sculptor, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Hughes, Gary, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Hunt, Richard - new sculptors to add, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Appendix A - Sculpture Removed, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - George Washington University, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Appendix A: Sculpture Removed - Franklin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Appendix - Sculptors - J. Seward Johnson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Research assistant - Mary Huntington, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Maps for suburbs, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Visiting sculpture - Spirit of Naval Aviation, 1994, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Introduction - L'Enfant and Fred. Douglas statues, 2008, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Appendix - lost scultures - social secur. eagles, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Limiting monuments, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Clark Mills, sculptor - part 1, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Clark Mills, sculptor - part 2, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Accent marks, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Binding stamp, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Corrections, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Corrections - Troxel - Nov. 2007, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Master list - Dec. 2007, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Photo permissions, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dust jacket - 3 selections, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Maps - correction - 11 May and 22 May, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence on Washington Sculpture, 1990-2007, Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Washington Post Sculpture, 07/25/2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sculpture correspondence 1980-2006, Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Save Outdoor Sculpture, 1997; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Francoise Yohalem, sculpture broker, 1997; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Park Service Sculpture Survey, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Hill Sculptures, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New sculptures 1974-1988, Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Kaempfer, developer, 1974-1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Article, sculpture authorization, Washington Post, 02/1989; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - World War I Memorial, 09/28/1995; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Roller-boarder at Eastern Market, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Sculpture article, Washington Post, 12/1987; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - National Capitol Memorial Comm. and Act of 1986, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Montgomery County public sculpture, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Article, Little Known DC Scupture, Washington Post, 1990; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Sculptures in the Parks booklet, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Office building sculpture, 1990; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Preface, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Introductiuon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Appendix II final, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Photos needed 09/2006, Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Photo credits, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - F-23 Epoch, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sculpture introduction, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Survey SIRIS (1), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Survey SIRIS (2), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Indoor sculpture, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ackmowledgements, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Grant, Maggie, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - GSA art program, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Museum of American Art, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Kiplinger Foundation, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Introduction - DC Commission on the Arts, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Johns Hopkins University Press, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Steve Troxel memos, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Johns Hopkins University Press memos, 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - JHU - Kathy Alexander, 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Robert Wiser, 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Folger Shakespeare Library, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - N-20 The Thief, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - 05 The Angel Moroni, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - H-20 Ancestor - Phillips Collection, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Dual Form - Phillips Collection, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Research Assistants - Mary Huntington, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Research Assistants - Linda Lowenstein, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Memorials, lectures on, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - De Weldon biography, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - J. Seward Johnson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New sculptures - text completed 2004, Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - SOS - DC inventory, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NPS inventory, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - New sculptures 1974-1988, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Wendy Ross, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, S. Seward, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - E- 38 - Columbia Abstract, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - E- 45 Home Plate, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - I - 4 - Armillary Sphere, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Master list old, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Carlyle Towers, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Seward Johnson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Apartment houses - Memorial Overlook, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Draft [1 of 7], circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Draft [2 of 7], circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Draft [3 of 7], circa 2005 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Draft [4 of 7], circa 2005 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Draft [5 of 7], circa 2005 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Draft [6 of 7], circa 2005 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Draft [7 of 7], circa 2005 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - First Draft [1 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - First Draft [2 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - First Draft [3 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - First Draft [4 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - First Draft [5 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - First Draft [6 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - First Draft [7 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - First Draft [8 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - First Draft [9 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - First Draft [10 of 10], 2006; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Second and Final Draft [1 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Second and Final Draft [2 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Second and Final Draft [3 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Second and Final Draft [4 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Second and Final Draft [5 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Second and Final Draft [6 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Second and Final Draft [7 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Second and Final Draft [8 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Second and Final Draft [9 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Second and Final Draft [10 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Second and Final Draft [11 of 11], 2007; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Draft / Foul partial A [1 of 4], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Draft / Foul partial A [2 of 4], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Draft / Foul partial A [3 of 4], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Draft / Foul partial A [4 of 4], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Draft / Foul MS partial B [1 of 5], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Draft / Foul MS partial B [2 of 5], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Draft / Foul MS partial B [3 of 5], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Draft / Foul MS partial B [4 of 5], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Draft / Foul MS partial B [5 of 5], circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Foul MS legends, circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Captions for photographs, circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Index draft, circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Index, circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Other drafts / proofs, circa 2006 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Page proofs uncorrected [1 of 5], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Page proofs uncorrected [2 of 5], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Page proofs uncorrected [3 of 5], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Page proofs uncorrected [4 of 5], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Page proofs uncorrected [5 of 5], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Corrected proofs [1 of 4], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Corrected proofs [2 of 4], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Corrected proofs [3 of 4], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Corrected proofs [4 of 4], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Master revised copy [1 of 5], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Master revised copy [2 of 5], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Master revised copy [3 of 5], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Master revised copy [4 of 5], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Master revised copy [5 of 5], circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Corrected page proofs [1 of 6], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Corrected page proofs [2 of 6], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Corrected page proofs [3 of 6], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Corrected page proofs [4 of 6], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Corrected page proofs [5 of 6], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Corrected page proofs [6 of 6], 08/2008; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Unbound copy proof [1 of 3], 2008; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Unbound copy proof [2 of 3], 2008; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Unbound copy proof [3 of 3], 2008; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Magazines, 2008; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Digital Proofs (oversized), 2008; Series 2 (Box 30, Item 1)
  - New page proofs (oversized), 2008; Series 2 (Box 30, Item 2)
  - Digital proofs (oversized), 2008; Series 2 (Box 31, Item 1)
  - Sculpture - Letters, 1993-2006; Series 2 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Sculpture - Articles, 1973-2015; Series 2 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Sculpture, 2006-2013; Series 2 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Silver, 1982; Series 2 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- American self-portraits, 1905-1994; 1980-1990; Series 3; 3.5 Linear Feet
  Prints and negatives are arranged into five binders. Other papers are arranged chronologically.
  The materials of this series include prints, photograph negatives, records, essays, museum publications, and magazines. They range in date from 1905 to 1999, but the bulk of the material dates from 1980 to 1999. The prints or photographs of self-portraits by American artists that were collected by James Goode. The other papers relate to his collection.
  - Self-portraits A-L (binder of prints), 1940-1994; Series 3 (Box 33, Item 1)
  - Self-portraits M-Z (binder of prints), 1905-1990; Series 3 (Box 33, Item 2)
  - Hickory Museum A-L (binder of prints), 1971-1992; Series 3 (Box 34, Item 1)
  - Hickory Museum M-Z (binder of prints), 1928-1992; Series 3 (Box 34, Item 2)
  - Negatives to photographs, 1995; Series 3 (Box 35, Item 1)
  - Self portraits, 1990-1996; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Self portraits - Cousineau, circa 1994; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Self portraits - Sidney Lawrance, Museum and Arts, Washington Magazine, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Catalog, self-portrait collection, 1990; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Self-portraits given to Hickory Museum of Art, 1992; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Donation of self-portraits to Hickory Museum of Art, 1992; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - History of Self-portraits by James Goode, 1993; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Self-portraits exhibition at the National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Magazine, 09/1993; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Review of self-portraits exhibition at the National Portrait Gallery, 1993; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Self-portraits article, American Artist, 1997; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Self-portraits, Mark Leithauser, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Catalog, sale of self-portraits, Weschlers, 1998; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Catalog, sale of self-portraits, Sloans, 1999; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Catalog, sale of self-portraits, Freemans, 1999; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Sale of self-portraits, 1999; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Kennedy-Warren Apartment House, circa 2006; Series 4; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series currently consists of one typed manuscript. More material may be added to this series in the future.
  This series currently consists of a typed manuscript, which dates from 2006. The manuscript is a history written by James Goode about the Kennedy-Warren apartment house, Washington, DC. More material may be added to this series in the future. And there are also pictures of Apt. 202 taken in 2013.
  - History of the Kennedy-Warren Apartment House, Past and Present [1 of 3], 08/2006; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - History of the Kennedy-Warren Apartment House, Past and Present [2 of 3], 08/2006; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - History of the Kennedy-Warren Apartment House, Past and Present [3 of 3], 08/2006; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of apartment 202, 2013; Series 4 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    General
    Photographs taken by Bruce M. White Caldwell, New Jersey
  - Kennedy-Warren apts 202, 2013; Series 4 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Photographs, slides and awards, circa 1860-2009; Series 5; 16.5 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series include framed awards, framed and unframed photographs, slides, diplomas, and albums of photographs. Many of the photographs are unidentified, but include images of the Goode family, architecture, national and international vacations, and various special events. They range in date from circa 1860-2009. The awards and diplomas were presented to James Goode.
  This series is arranged into three subseries: Photographs, Slides, and Framed photographs and awards.
  - Photographs, circa 1860-2009; Series 5 Subseries 1
    Arrangement
    Arranged chronologically.
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains unframed photographs and negatives. The subject matter includes vacations, family, and architecture. Most of the photographs are unidentified. The photographs range in date from circa 1860-2009.
    - James Goode family, circa 1860-circa 1920; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 1)